Sir,
Hey, hey.
Why did you stop this car here?
You cannot stop this car here, sir.
This is a position for basketball crew.
I am a basketball coach.
O master "smart".
- What?
Are you really a basketball coach?
- Yes.
- So show me how to pay this basket.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
- Good luck.
- And you, too.
- And you too, sir.
Good morning.
Is this the time of coming?
The oldest coach came early and
sat here, and the assistant comes.
What do you want if you want
to come at seven in the morning?
Sir, did your wife come this time?
It is busy.
Watch the players a man for a man.
Wait a minute.
Pass the ball to Dave,
pass the ball to Dave.
- Sidhath, passed the ball to Dave. How does
it pass it and Dave is not at its level?
Look at this.
- Pass the ball to Dave again.
- Golshan, this is enough.
Come, count.
Pass, pass.
- Your strategy is wrong, sir, if you listen to me...
- Be quiet.
Go and sit there.
Faster, pass the ball.
Come on, come.
Come on Dave, hit.
- How did Ravan died, my brother?
- What sir?
How did Raven die?
- I don't know, sir.
- Vichan said...
- "Oh Brabho, instill the weapon in his Sareeh directly."
- Pay attention, guys.
- Pay attention.
- The gods listen to everyone.
- Yes, sir.
- However, this is just a human being.
- Pay attention, guys. He is also
from the Delhi region and its environs.
Hurry up, return, return.
The problem is over, the game ended.
The game ended in dropping the ball.
Be quiet.
Keep a beginner coach as you are.
Let the older coach coach as an old coach.
- You want to take my place, right?
- Yes, I want it.
- You want to be the main coach, right?
- Yes, yes, I want that.
He paid in that basket and show me, dwarf.
Sir, sir.
I am strange to my face.
In the International Basketball
Championship that was held in Delhi today...
We also saw a simple fight.
Because of his insult to his
short stature, the assistant...
Do you lead while you are drunk, you fool?
To stop.
Stop, if I hold you, I will cut you off.
Are you crazy, fool?
I was shocked twice.
What is there, brother?
Is this a suitable
place to stop the car?
Show me your license.
Don't you know how to
lead? Show me your license.
Sir, he has no old records.
He is a good man, sir.
Who among us does not make mistakes, sir?
The case is now definitely registered.
You will have to go to
court, so he fell and left.
So, Master, the drunk, is
it awake from your secret?
Come on, brother, fall here.
- What dilemma did you put yourself in my brother?
- Do you not have any shame?
Didn't you even think about your mother?
Didn't I be able to save you last night?
- I am sorry, man.
Why do I apologize, you fool?
Am I the one who told you
to lead while you are drunk?
Listen, brother, the
court session tomorrow.
Do not say any nonsense before the judge.
The heart must be great,
sir, but I have forgiven him.
Let him forgive me too.
Sir, these things are very normal.
Let's forget the matter.
Above all, when you are one
family, such things happen, isn't it sir?
He also did not harm.
If he lost his eye, or his
ear split, or he became
deaf, I would have left my
job myself, but in this case...
It is just a simple
scratch, sir, that's all.
Ya Paswan G, he would
have made a police report.
- He agreed after a great persuasion.
- He agreed, right?
So it is fine, sir.
Oh Araora G, you are
very good as a coach.
For this reason I have
endured all this yet, but I can not.
You will stop working for some time.
- You have been stopped.
- What?
I?
I was stopped from work?
I can't believe, this is great.
A wound to the back is
better than going to prison.
I only drank this fate, man.
I will do my best to save you from prison.
- I will make you do a community service.
- Well, what is this?
These days, not everyone
is sent to prison in all cases.
Some are sent to do
community service as well.
Good.
She looks beautiful when she
wears this tie, looks respectable.
Your case went to the most hatred judge.
So do not say any nonsense at all.
- I will say what to say and what should not be said, stay silent.
- Well, well.
Sir, I will not come
with the elevator... I...
- I will use stairs.
- Did not?
No, no, I cannot come with the elevator.
- Golshan, we will delay, come quickly.
- What floor?
The third floor.
- Well, well.
Golshan Aroura, Ibn Harman Arora.
Although you are a responsible citizen in society,
you have led your car under the influence of alcohol.
You broke the rear lamp of
government vehicle No. DL 761232.
She quarreled with the
policeman Hattaram.
I sang songs against the
law and the constitution?
Yes, Madam, he sang a
song called "Blind Law".
This is mentioned in the police statement.
Did you know that you may
face a two -year prison sentence?
Two years? Madam, does the punishment
reach this limit for something like this?
Sorry, sir, sorry, madam.
Because of your clean record and being your first
crime, this court does not want to send you to prison.
Do you know what is the community service?
Yes, madam.
Do you know about people
with mental disabilities?
About crazy?
Those with mental disabilities!
This means that the mental and physical development of people with
a failure in mental development is different from ordinary people.
Use the correct words
when talking about them.
So, Golshan Aroura...
Ibn Harnam Aroura, all the
charges against you have been proven.
But the court wants to direct
your talent to the right place.
The court recommends that you
train for a period of three months for a
basketball team with intellectual disabilities - to train them.
- Three months?
My lady, should I study
crazy for three months?
- And a fine of 500 rupees.
- 500 rupees?
- To say crazy?
- 1000 rupees.
- Everyone calls them
crazy. 2000 rupees.
What is the mistake
in the words of crazy?
5000 rupees.
A fine of 5000 rupees
imposed on you.
- What a donkey.
- What is this?
Can I call crazy crazy? Don't say that,
why do you say anything to anyone?
Am I the only one who
says that? Everyone says.
What is wrong with that?
What has just happened?
Do not say black black.
Don't say to Chinese Chinese,
do not say the crazy crazy.
Do not say a dwarf.
What do I say then?
Wait a minute.
Nobody is a 5 -foot and 8 -inch dwarf.
But it is also considered 5 feet and 6 inches long, and for
this reason you say that you are taller in two descendants?
My mom!
Who is joking with his family?
We do this with strangers.
Why is anyone considered strange?
There are no strangers, son.
Everyone is people.
Is she your son's wife?
- Yes.
Answer, there may be
a problem with the store.
I don't want to talk.
Your pride will destroy your home.
Do not worry about me.
I do not worry about it,
but I worry about myself.
He left his house and lives in
the external room in my home,
I was getting a rent of
10,000 per month from it.
Is it not it Dalaat G?
Ten thousand five hundred. Look,
say ten thousand five hundred.
Who asked you? Take care of
your work and do not interfere.
Go and bring some tea. My
mom, I will give you your rent.
- That's it.
Do not bark like a dog.
Barking bark...
Hey Dalaat G, prepare for me tea as well.
How much, brother...
What can be better than the coming of a
professional coach like you to teach children?
Because other sports
cause them some problems.
They cannot do many things together.
They cannot remember much of the rules.
Basketball is a little easier.
On them just take the
ball and put it in the basket.
She won medals in other sports as well.
All of these are from
slow bicycle race... this.
And those certificates
from the Kerem game.
I will show you the prizes that you won
in the "Antakshiri" singing competition.
Good, good.
So, how many days a week will come?
One day.
One day a week is more than
enough, it is not good to get the children.
One day?
If so, I will talk to Anu.
Anu?
The one that knows
you, is what sent you here.
- Who is Anu?
- Her nephew here too.
- What do you do?
- Judge.
My daughter Anu,
Mr. Golshan came here.
He is a very good man.
He says he will come one day a week.
Welcome.
No, not my lady, there
must be a misunderstanding.
Not one day a week, but
every day a week, Carter Baji.
No, no, not the problem of
my lady, this is completely true.
Carter Bage is very nice, very good.
Well, my lady, goodbye.
We are about to hold a national
championship for distinguished people.
Now that you are our coach,
we have made a request.
National championship
...people will laugh.
Don't tell anyone about this.
I did not tell anyone that
you were punished here.
I could have escaped punishment.
I have three lawyers in
my house, do you know?
When I heard about children,
I felt some compassion.
I mean, they are also human, right?
I thought that if I went and did
something, it would be good for them.
They will learn something, the poor.
Poor.
My name Golshan Aroura.
For the next three
months, I am your coach.
I know that it is difficult for you to
understand what is said to you...
So, if you don't
understand anything...
Raise your hands and
say: "Please explain", well?
What?
I don't hear what he says.
First, say: "Please explain.
- "Please explain."
- Raise your hand...
"Please explain.
Nothing, he says the
new coach is a donkey.
Well, say your names.
Generous...
- Satper.
- Lotus.
Lotus? Is your name Lotus?
Kamal Sir.
But he wants to be English.
So we call him Lotus
as a matter of love.
I Godo, and this Panto.
Sunil.
Hargovind.
Raju.
"Please explain.
Sharma G.
So well, let's start training.
Quraishi...
- What?
He just finished
saying his name.
Karim Quraishi.
Well, now...
Let's start with simple exercises
that you can even do, well?
Let's start passing the ball.
Sorry, sorry.
Perhaps passing the
ball is not that easy.
Do something, divide into
husbands... Choose someone.
Sir, I have a sweetheart
from the beginning.
- if? How can I be
with someone else?
His girlfriend is a hay seam.
Yes, then? A passion for
fancy can have a lover, right?
Do not say that word.
Which word?
- "Hui Seller".
- So why do you say it?
I just explain.
So I was also explaining.
His girlfriend is a hay seam.
I told you not that word,
say something else.
What?
Say it works in the
field of "business".
Business lady, well?
Do you also have a sweetheart?
I have a wife.
What do you do?
She works in the
field of "business".
Me too.
You are the two, come here.
Take a ball.
Take one ball.
I, I...
No, no, close your mouths.
- What is it?
- He went.
- Where did he go?
- He lost his way.
He will return shortly.
Wait a little.
Sir, you have come
back, you can talk now.
Why do you wear
...leather shoes?
- Because it fits my helmet.
Next time, wear a sneakers.
- Also, you will not need a helmet.
- Truly?
That fan is above,
What if I fell to my head?
Hug me, you must embrace me.
Get away, what to do? Get away.
Go back.
Come on, they were
divided into pairs, two two.
Sir, I have a sweetheart
from the beginning.
His girlfriend is a hay seam.
Do not be divided into anything.
Go back to your
places, lined up, let's go.
Nobody says anything,
they remained silent.
Now, hold the balls.
These poor people?
These are terrorists.
Who sympathizes with them?
When did you say they are poor?
- You are the one who said that.
- Yes, so how can I form a team?
The team consists
of ordinary people.
Coach, tell me something.
When you were eight years
old, were you normal or different?
I was normal.
So, doctors say their ability to learn
is at the level of a 8-10-year-old child.
At that age, this happens, one
cannot become conservative, right?
Yes, but staying at the age of 8-10 years
is not always an ordinary matter, man?
Coach, tell me what is this?
This, this... tell
me what it is.
Say, please tell
me what is this.
It is part of the body.
My body or your body?
Everyone has.
Yes, now I understand
this is normal.
I understand that this is normal, and then you will
understand that every person has their own nature.
Just as it is normal for the
policeman to hit the thieves.
It is also natural for the
thief to receive beating.
And as it is natural
for the politician to lie.
As is natural for the
public, they discover lying.
Or, as it is normal
for the beggar to beg.
And as it is normal
for the rich to boast.
Everyone adheres to
its own nature, coach.
Your nature is for you,
and their nature for them.
How much sugar you need?
- At the normal rate.
- My nature or your nature?
Put six tablespoons.
That's why I was wondering
how I became a nice man like this.
Greetings, Greetings.
Congratulations.
Our congratulations!
Greetings, aunt.
Hello dear, looks
very beautiful.
O Golshan, when
will Sonita return?
Back... it is the one who left the
house... it is the one you should return.
What happened?
Do you have an affair or what?
No, no, of course, what is this?
Yes, who may have
an affair with you?
Certainly it is the
relationship Sonita, right?
What do you mean "who may have a
relationship with me"? What is missing me?
Sonita is the one you should
say what is missing you, right?
In any case, will you separate?
This is our personal issue,
what is your relationship?
No, if you were
separating, tell me.
That is my cousin,
I will arrange with Sonita.
He is an absolute, innocent,
and desperate man...
And white skin.
And Radib is
much longer than it...
Eat spring coils before you
go, it's very delicious, well?
Come, come, children
...where are you going?
It is not that
length, it is like us...
- I am going, man.
- It is delirious, listen...
Ascend to the upper floor
...I will bring you "ninety ml".
Sixty, sixty... thirty,
thirty... Please, please.
Welcome.
How does the
training of players go?
I talk to my mother every day.
Yes, he is going well.
Did the couple give some
money on the basement?
- Yes...
- My God, I also gave them, now the amount is double.
Oh, my God.
We didn't meet a week ago, and
you worry about the amount you gave?
Sorry.
How much was it given?
- 2100.
- 2100?
Who gives 2100? I
will go and retrieve it.
Oh my God, wait.
Forget it.
Moreover, you are suspended.
Why do you waste money?
You don't have a
financial problem, right?
No, no problem at all.
Even if there is a problem, when
we can talk about problems...
What is the problem
that I did not talk about?
About us.
- Are we a problem? So
what are we, Golshan?
We are a couple.
If we are a couple, then
why don't we live together?
If we are a couple, why did you leave
your house and go to your mother's house?
I went before you
asked me to go.
You?
Does a person marry someone
to expel him from the house?
Why can we not be
together Golshan?
I miss you.
Also, what do I want?
I just want Golshan small...
A person with eyes similar
to your eyes completely.
The same hadith again?
I said a hundred times,
I don't want a child.
Do you want to quarrel again?
When will you quarrel?
- You will leave anyway .. So, do you
say that we should quarrel every day?
One must fight the world
Sonita, who is fighting himself?
If you and I quarrel, whatever the winner
is, it is our relationship that will lose.
So any world cup we won
because of our relationship?
We are still not even.
Above all, I caused
you to stop work.
I did not stop working
at my own free will.
You cannot take care of your work,
and you cannot take care of your home.
Wonderful, wonderful, you took
care of your work perfectly, right?
"I will become an actress, I will become an actress,
I will enter the world of films," what happened?
You are running my
mother's store, right?
I gave up acting
due to marriage.
So, did you ask you
to give up acting?
What is the relationship of
representation with marriage?
It becomes difficult
for girls, Golshan.
This is something
you will not understand.
Why? Why will I not understand?
Because you never
understand anyone's view.
Amazing...
If anyone in this world...
Teach you how to understand what
another person says, this is enough.
You do not speak, and
do not respond to my calls.
Do not respond to my messages.
Do you know, Golshan, how...
Remember yesterday's
eggs... yes, eggs are.
How do you like it... Advice or
fried... or added to Al -Biriani?
Well guys, today we will start
with some warm -up exercises.
Well, everyone runs
up straight... well?
Sir, my nose a little
crooked, what do I do about it?
Well, the nose is not straight.
Let us all in a straight line.
But... sir.
If the door is
the straight thing,
Do we deviate right or...
Yes, yes, well, well, run
in a straight line, agreed?
Come on, lined up.
Relax your bodies.
Yes, wonderful.
Take a breath from the nose.
And forgive the mouth, well?
Quietly.
- Yes, sir. Right line.
Well guys, wonderful.
Excellent.
Relax your hands.
Wonderful, wonderful.
Very good... keep.
Where did they go?
What does this say?
Are you the husband
of the judge's daughter?
I told the provincial judge not
to come to my court without a tie.
Court ethics apply to Indian
administrative service officers as well.
Go now.
Greetings, madam...
Madam, I cannot train that team.
Do you want to return to prison?
No, no, feet the lawsuit.
I am ready to pay any fine.
Look, you waste
my time and time.
Really, aunt?
- What did you say?
- Maternal aunt..
Because you issued the
ruling as a code, not as a judge.
That is why you sent me to where
your daughter's husband is studying.
You did not punish me.
You have arranged a private
lesson for your daughter's husband.
It made a mistake.
And it must be corrected.
I had to...
I send you to clean the floors in the
emergency department of a government hospital,
Or something like that.
Many people come there,
Because people like you are
driving their cars while they are drunk.
Do I send you?
No, no, my lady, the sorry of
my lady, you have misunderstood.
In fact, I love your daughter's
husband so much, he is very nice...
Your daughter's husband
is my daughter's husband...
Your daughter's
husband is great...
Hello?
Sir, we got acceptance.
You got what?
Sir, we got acceptance...
in the national championship.
Because we have a
coach... I mean, we have.
Carter Bage, is this something
you should say at five in the morning?
I'm sorry, I should have
told you earlier, right?
I thought you might be asleep.
Because, as you know, a person wakes
up from his sleep is not a good thing.
Well, congratulations...
Thank you, sir ..
- No, thank you.
I see you soon, my coach...
How did you wake
up very early today?
- And why all these lights are illuminated?
- There was a call from Carter Baji.
This team will participate
in the tournament.
They may also win.
Mom, what do I want if
these crazy people win or not?
Why? Why is it
important for you?
You are their coach, they are
your team, they are your players...
Do not go like this
in basketball, mom.
in basketball, son.
How can you say
that? Short tall...
My height is not
short... I am average.
Yes, average in Lajt Nakhir.
But for basketball,
you are short.
Such a finger...
The smaller finger that
indicates that you need to urinate.
Yes, what if he was
young, talent exists, right?
- Who saw your talent?
- My coaches saw it.
Hey... your coach was not
even prepared to look at your face.
He did not want to perform a short
player's performance experience.
I cried, begged... I
slapped him on his face.
At that time, just have the
performance experience.
See, son.
There are people who
are different from others.
And they must fight
for a person for them.
I fought for you.
You are fighting for them.
O boy.
Turn off the lights
and go to sleep.
I am the one who
pays the electricity bill.
If you bothered you a lot,
I will go and stay in a hotel.
Do not say that, son...
It sends hope in my heart.
They all grabbed
the balls... no.
basketball rollers.
Good.
Now we will train
on payment, well?
One by one, put the
ball in the basket, well?
One by one.
- Are you ready, guys?
- Well, sir.
Start.
Oh my God, I said
one by one, right?
- my lord... Yes, Karim
did not throw the ball.
Karim A good boy.
Now Karim will put the ball
in the basket, right Karim?
Yes, sir ..
What are you doing?
Come, take all a
5 -minute break.
Drink some water, calm down...
Hargovind
- Give me the ball...
- for me...
Give me the ball...
- What are you doing?
- Give me the ball.
Hey, what are you doing?
What is this?
Stop.
Shut up.
Training is canceled,
all go to your homes.
Sharma G.
Well, well, I'm fine.
Thanks.
Go too, enough for today, well?
Thank you.
Hargovind, I know that their
families send them all here,
So they can meet people,
make friends, and spend time.
But we will participate in
a competition, starring...
The championships are not
to spend time, but to win them.
I know you are
smarter than them.
And a much better player.
But you cannot train
on your own all the time.
If you play with the team,
We can win, and we
can defeat everyone.
Do not give up the
team, oh Hargovind.
Sir, coach ..
What is your problem?
I have Down syndrome, my
face is different from others.
I find it difficult to read what
is written on the blackboard.
I am thinking that I may
have many diseases.
Sometimes I urinate
in bed during sleep.
Two days ago, they also
cut the cable TV subscription.
No, no, what is the problem now?
Now this shoe does not
suit me, what do I do about it?
Instead.
I replace them, but I lost
the bill that the store gave me.
Oh my God, instead
with each other.
Put this shoe in that foot
and that shoe in this foot.
Good.
Oh my God, sit and do that.
Sir, the coach, my
feet became fine.
Not the feet, the
shoe... forget.
Because, as you
know, somewhat stupid.
No, no, I did not say that,
when did you say that?
I remember, you called
me With "smart master".
I remember... I remember.
Hargovind should be
involved in playing everywhere.
Hargovind left the team.
What do you mean
by leaving the team?
He wakes up every day at four
in the morning and goes to work...
We had only one good
player, and now who will play?
The rest of the team will play.
Oh my God, the rest is useless,
they are not suitable for anything.
Sir, coach.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Farewell.
See... see there.
Sir, he is not a man, he is
like a drunk person at a party.
His hands go in a direction,
and put him in another direction.
No consistency, no
rhythm, nothing...
Where does that
crazy go to his bike?
Oh my God, to stop it.
This man will kill
someone today... hey, hey.
He left.
That "useless" has not
caused any accident to this day.
Did you do?
It may be difficult to control
the ball, but self -control is not.
He lives in a hostel
away from his family.
It works in the
kitchen of Absara.
- What to do, man,
faster. Sorry, sir.
"I am faster, I apologize.
The Raju family has a shed, spending
his whole day speaking to the plants.
O stubborn aloe vera, other than your
nature, why do you drink all this water?
Hey, Raju.
A wide smile, oh Raju...
Although Raju was born in Delhi, his style
is completely similar to the style of air.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Farewell.
Oh Baji, how are you?
Goodbye, my children, did
you think your nails or not?
- Yes, yes.
- How did you tell her?
- Thus.
- No.
- good.. Do not
cut it like this.
- Well, sorry.
- Well, go, goodbye... wonderful.
Is everything well, sir?
- Everything is fine.
Satber mechanic
in his uncle garage.
Not any mechanic.
It is very talented.
This is "useless"...
Mechanical engineering
students teach cars.
Use ethylene glycol.
Otherwise, this car
will heat excessively.
Yes, write down that.
Goodbye Sharma G.
Charma G's mother is dead.
He lives with his
father and uncle.
It is preferred for everyone.
Sharma G.
Yes, I ..
This "useless" works in a café.
If any customer understands
what he says, gets a 10%discount.
Thank you Sharma G.
Old customers understand
it well, I don't know how.
- Truly?
- Yes.
- Goodbye Baji, goodbye to the coach.
- Goodbye Lotus.
Goodbye Lotus.
Lotus works in a dyeing factory.
- Sir, this leaks?
- Truly?
Keep it, son. Thank
you, sir... Thank you.
That is why it comes
every day as a yellow bird.
Gudo loves animals a lot.
And animals likelihood.
He works on an animal
farm, he is an animal expert.
This "useless" takes care of animals
that no one else can take care of.
It is always with animals.
Really, is this reason that
the bad smell is emitted from it?
No, no, this is because
it does not bathe.
- I will hold it and bath it one day.
- No no.
When he was a child, he
almost drowned and was saved.
For this reason he
is afraid of water.
The problem is not
water, the problem is fear.
Sir, do I suffer from a fever?
Let me see.
No.
Oh my God, this
cannot be true, sir.
Sir, do I suffer from a fever?
No.
It's okay, I will
fulfill myself.
Oh, my God...
Why is the journey of Delhi
- Mumbai is very late, sir?
How India will become a
great power, I will go and see.
Not that, everything is normal.
Natural.
Natural?
My God, many people feel that they
have this or that disease... Sonel too.
I am not talking about it.
Seeing a plane in the
sky and checking its timing.
This is madness, right, Baji?
Is looking at a mad plane?
Yes...
Many people hide
behind the trees...
And they monitor the birds with an endoscope
for hours, calling them "bird monitors".
Why don't they call them crazy?
Some people collect stamps
and stick them in a notebook.
And they stare for hours.
Why do they not call them
crazy, but rather call them stamps.
Each person has his own
nature, their own passion.
Everyone has a story.
Some did not develop
properly during pregnancy...
Others suffered
complications at birth...
Our destiny is not in
the lines of our palm, sir,
Rather, it is written
in our chromosomes.
What does that mean?
It means that the body has cells, and in
each cell there are 23 pairs of chromosomes.
The color of our
eyes, our hair color...
Our length, all these things are
determined by chromosomes...
In each chromosome, two
characters, such as Seta and Geta.
- A true copy?
- Exactly.
The problem occurs when
there are three instead of two.
For example, when there are three
copies of chromosome number 21,
Down syndrome occurs.
I mean, if one
chromosome moved a little...
To this event for you, or me.
"Useful"...
Then there is autism... and Tourette
syndrome, there is a full spectrum.
How do these things happen?
Sir, the coach, sit with
their families for 10 minutes.
They will tell you
better than Google.
What about Hargovind?
What is his problem,
it seems normal?
Even the cold varies
from person to person.
A person has a more running
in the nose, and the last.
Someone sneezes ten times,
and the last hundred times.
Hargovind is better
than others, right,
But think about it, it's on the
same train... but in a background.
Invisible autism.
Why left the team?
This is another story.
I will tell you at another time.
Go guys.
Wonderful... wonderful, go.
Oh my God, do you miss again?
No, no sir, see, nest a bird.
Panto, why do you
rub your ear all the time?
The time passes
quickly when I do this, sir.
Time passes quickly?
However, you should
stop for some time to do so.
Wonderful Panto, wonderful Godo.
Lotus, the knees down...
Sunil... Why don't
you use your right hand?
Tennis facility here
...tennis attachment.
So well, do it with one hand.
Sharma G, great.
Raju, I liked it.
Thank you, sir.
After this, we will train
to pass the ball, well?
How, sir?
I will explain that later.
Oh my God, no...
So guys, tomorrow our
first match. Sorry, sir, sorry.
Come Karim.
Tomorrow, that is, on
Monday... our first match.
The biggest difference in this
match is that we will play on our land.
What if the TV crashes at home?
Let it be destroyed, they
cut my cable anyway.
No problem at all...
I mean at home... our land.
We will play here, where we
all train every day, our land.
Sir, Hargovind is not even here?
Hargovind... Hargovind...
Guodo, do you need a reminder?
Sorry.
Now listen to the strategy.
Good.
There is one important thing.
Each of you has three colors.
- One red, one blue, and the other white sir.
- Yes, correct.
For tomorrow's match,
you will all wear blue, well?
Sir, if I wear blue,
then my mother...
You will not get to know me.
And then, sir, my
love, loves red?
She is a passionate seller.
Sir, I said not
to use this word.
Yes, sir said we do
not use this word.
She is practicing a business,
just like my sir's wife, isn't it sir?
- Hey.
- I will wear red.
How to wear red, the other
team is the one who wears red?
So I will play with
the other team.
I will only wear red.
Wear blue...
- No, red...
- Shut up.
Hey, shut up.
Shut up, I will wear red.
- I love my mother.
- Shut up.
Shut up.
Tomorrow, everyone wearing
the blue color of the match.
What does Carter Bage,
Despite the presence of all these chairs, who
will come to watch a match on Monday morning?
My friend, friends will
come... families will come.
When a child is born
like this in the family,
It must be very
difficult, right?
Yes, of course it is.
But everything
beautiful is difficult.
When a child is born
like this in a house,
How is this beautiful or good?
Sir, the coach, the homes are
completely similar to humans.
And like humans, it does
not take time for sheikh.
Children grow up and leave the
house, the sheikh of the house.
Every house needs
a little childhood.
It is true that their
families find it very difficult.
They cannot go on vacation,
they cannot watch a movie.
Sometimes they feel very tired.
But this is also true...
As far as these
children are difficult,
They never call the house old.
Their families and friends
love them very much.
Coach, today is Monday.
Even if it was the
last day in the world ..
Everyone will come
to watch the match.
- Baji.
- Yes.
Where do I put it?
- On the left.
Didn't I tell you that
you will wear blue shirts?
No, I said red.
No, no, the coach said.
So why did you come in red?
My mother cannot
distinguish me in blue.
I have color blindness,
which color I wear, sir?
Everyone in the team
must wear the same color.
At least Sharma
G wears blue pants.
Sir, Karim did not come today.
His boss did not give him leave.
He is a very bad person ..
I know, but what to do now?
We can wear red.
No.
Judo ..
What is there, sir?
You have two blue shirts, right?
Take off the one inside
and give it to Lotus.
Even if I die, I will
not wear this shirt.
If you want to play, the
Judo shirt is bounced.
The rest is back to you.
- What about Satper? I
do not have a blue shirt.
Hey, pass the ball ..
My mother .. mom,
how are you, mom?
My mom Satbir, look, mom ..
- Come here.
- I?
- I Satbir.
- Yes, I know ..
But tell me who made
you wear this shirt?
Satber, go and play
.. Focus on the game.
- I gave him a different shirt to wear.
- Now, defenders, let's defend ..
Wonderful wonderful.
Hey, genius.
Do not take a month
to wash one dish.
Move your hand quickly.
Will your mother
come to clean the floor?
But my mother died
a long time ago, sir.
How can she come?
Didn't you say that you will
give a holiday for the match?
Yes, and I am the Minister
of Sports .. O small ass.
Really, it is wrong
to pity anyone.
Now, a triangular defense ..
At an angle of 45 degrees, rush.
Defense of the region, rush
...the defense of the region.
Take it and take the ball.
Two assortment-one-two guys ..
District defense.
What does the coach say?
I do not know what he says, it is necessary
to have something about basketball.
Lotus, pass to the
advanced position, faster.
Raju, put a barrier
for the ball holder.
Put a barrier for
the ball holder.
Two assortment-one-two
guys .. Play two-one-two.
District defense.
Wonderful guys.
Wonderful basket,
wonderful guys.
Good shot ..
Come on, guys ..
Wonderful .. Sharma G, pass
to the advanced center, wonderful.
Amazing amazing
.. wonderful guys ..
This is a mistake.
This is a mistake, why
doesn't he count a mistake?
O judgment... wrong.
Lotus, pass to Satbir.
- What?
- Quickly, give it to Satper.
Error .. error.
Wonderful .. wonderful.
A free throw to
Satber .. a free throw.
Mistake..
Wonderful Satper.
Do not be terrified, focus.
Satber .. This throw
will make us win.
It is a very important
throw, do not scare... focus.
Satber .. This throw
is very important.
With this one throw,
we can win the game.
Well, but you are afraid.
Hey, shut up... no one
interferes, Satbir will lose his focus.
Satbir .. Arjun only sees the
eye of the bird, did you understand?
Faster Satber, faster.
He paid it directly.
You are on a side, and the bird's eye is on the other
side .. with that single throw we can win the game.
Fast, Satber, don't be
afraid, keep your focus.
Sir, you are silent first.
Oh, my God!
We won ..
This is wonderful,
coach, the boys won.
Listen, listen ..
Where is the next
match? It is in Chandigar.
Shandigar .. Shandigar ..
Well, well, now take
a shower, wonderful.
- Bathe .. bathe.
- Be quiet.
- Bathe.
- Satper.
Why do you disturb him? You
know that he is afraid to shower, son ..
Judo, come here .. sit with me.
Sit.
Yes, wonderful Judo,
don't think about them.
Wonderful, we won ..
We won ..
Come on Judo, nothing will
happen, take a shower today, go.
No, I will die.
You will not die.
You will be happy when
you enter under the shower.
- I will die .. I know.
- Leave this.
Nothing will happen, my dear.
- A mouse, mouse, sir ..
- Mouse?
A mouse .. mouse ..
Hello mouse.
Hello mouse .. Hello.
The mouse... will die.
Sir, the mouse
will die... save it.
The mouse will die, save it.
Mouse.
No, I cannot save it
.. I am afraid of mice.
You love animals, right?
You alone can save it.
Look, it asks for your help.
The mouse calls you ..
Judo .. Help me die, save me ..
Judo ..
A mouse .. mouse.
I will save you ..
Wonderful, hold
the glasses Punto.
Yes, help Sonel
.. and you also help.
Take off the inner shirt, Sonel,
collective work... wonderful.
Wonderful, wonderful ..
Take off the shoe ..
Wonderful, and socks also ..
Faster, you have
to save the mouse.
Group work, they helped.
Judo, wonderful Judo.
Now you will save the mouse.
Go, Judo, save the
mouse... wonderful.
Judo ..
Mouse..
Mouse.
Save the mouse ..
I saved him ..
Judo, see where you are?
- In water ..
- Yes, nothing happened to you.
I saved the mouse.
Judo ..
Satber, bring soap quickly.
Yes, give me it.
Judo .. Today I overcame
your fear of water completely.
Now take a shower,
come on Judo ..
Hug me ..
Parsi .. Parsi ..
Where is Mrs. Parsi?
His name Rustam, kindly
say the name Gupta G.
My name is also Ashok,
madam, did you say it one day?
- Give me two minutes.
- Hey Parsi.
Ashok G.
- What did Rustom do?
- He brought the bus.
So what is the problem, the
whole world comes with a bus?
Rustam?
Madam, I made a trailer
from an old bus for rent.
Do you remember my lady, you have done a TV program?
- Yes.
- Only three episodes were filmed.
- Yes..
Two of them failed ..
- Yes, and what is that?
Yes, and what in that, you used the
makeup truck with this itself as well.
Yes, but what are
you doing here?
My lady, if she was at home,
my brother would take it.
He drives it quickly,
and breaks it.
So I stopped here quietly.
Now this bus will be
stopped here every day.
Hey, further vehicle.
What a man, being
Parsi and lives in Delhi.
- Gupta G kindly.
- He is from the people of Delhi as an authenticity of you.
No sentence does not
end without insulting.
- Do I complete the sentence?
- It is not physically.
Rustam.
Keep the vehicle, kindly.
What hurts your ass, Gupta,
as if there are vehicles here?
What does it mean?
Are you not coming
with us to Chandigar?
Should I and the boys go alone?
How to be alone,
You are with them
.. They are with you.
It is not that difficult, coach.
Can I ask something personal?
Yes.
Do you have children?
No.
So imagine for one day that
you have 8 children, well?
I have no desire to be a father.
What did you say?
I have no desire to be
a father Kartar Baji.
Sorry, what did you say?
I have no desire to be a father.
My father was not appropriate
to be a father, and I am.
Did you understand?
Also, I do not want
these personal questions.
Sorry.
- Welcome.
Hi, sir.
Hello sir.
The coach came
.. The coach came.
Another player is equipped
instead of Hargovind.
From?
Golo, Golo Khan.
- Good.
- Goodbye, coach, congratulations.
- Thanks.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello guys.
- Welcome.
Judo ..
- You are shining today.
- Powder.
He puts a baby
powder, even on his leg.
Where is the white outfit?
Here is..
Hey.
What do you do Judo?
Where is that new player?
- What is his name?
- Golo.
We played with him last year.
After that, we all
started to call "the bee".
- The bee?
- Golo Khan.
Golo .. Golo ..
Golo .. Golo.
Are you a girl?
What kind of fools?
This is the coach.
These are, Miss Golo Khan.
Hi Golo.
Do not flirt with the saying of
"Golo Golo", Saying Khan.
Well, sorry.
Well, but we are
going to play basketball.
Why did you bring
this surfing board?
What if there is a
pool at the hotel?
A hotel, any hotel .. we will return
in the evening after the match.
Who brought this
negative person?
- She came to herself.
- The bus arrived.
Come on, let's come to us,
the bus has arrived, let's come.
What day is it today?
Saturday.
Pedro .. Pedro ..
Raju, stop it.
Stop it.
Oh, my God..
Go, go.
Come on, stand in front of him.
At least stop it from behind.
Stop it.
Yes, yes, take it.
O man.
Pedro .. Pedro ..
Where Golo?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
Let anyone stop it.
O comrades, watch
it .. Oh my God.
Pedro .. Pedro ..
Where did you go?
To smoke a cigarette
.. It is forbidden here.
Dye Pedro... move forward.
Go, Pedro .. Go.
Wonderful Pedro .. wonderful.
O man, let one of you
stop this young man.
I can stop it.
So stop it.
A little or complete?
- Completely.
- Good..
Table, switching.
- Go.
- Raju.
Go.
Wonderful Pedro .. move forward.
Go, Pedro .. move forward.
Is this reason
they call it a fly?
I stopped it.
It is not a fly, sir, but a bee.
That stings.
Golo .. Golo ..
What is this
nonsense against hell?
Sit up.
Come here, do not
pay attention to that way.
I don't know what they
are exposed to the young.
I do not know how to free
people to ride a public bus.
Don't you have a separate bus?
- Shut up... shut down.
O team, we played
very well today.
We will win the next
match by more points.
Sir, when is the next match?
What, sir ..
Is this your girlfriend?
- No.
- Not possible.
Did not. Do I look like this?
I am not the worst, but
you are not Salman Khan.
Never, I am married.
Who?
- Sonita. Why didn't you come?
Cheerlings... a quarrel...
- A quarrel ..
- Shut up.
This is what happens
between them.
- What is happening?
- Sir mine.
Trains ..
You act as if you know what
is happening in married life.
- We know.
- We all know.
Sir, the only thing we do not
know is why people quarrel.
When the fight
begins, it never ends.
Yes, even if you quarrel,
why doesn't it end up?
It is not easy
to finish a fight.
It is easy.
You do not know how to end it.
What do you do?
- Sorry.
- Any sorry?
I saw so it ends, when
you say sorry, it must end.
Lotus, did not harm, right?
What do you say, say it clearly.
What are you saying?
My brother, who
is this, take it back.
- Sharma G.
- Yes.
What nonsense do you do?
- Who threw gum?
- Powder ..
Hey, little actor, shut up.
Or go down.
Go down, or I will make
the mouse bite you.
O mad ass.
I will take off my
shoes and give you it.
Brother, brother, First,
speak with respect.
Tell them to stop the song.
Why do we stop the song?
Because this is
forbidden in this bus.
Smoking is prohibited in
this bus, smoking is forbidden.
The spit is forbidden, but where is
it written that singing is forbidden?
Do I show you a full bus map?
They should have a separate bus.
This is a bus for ordinary
people, not a crazy clinic.
- Madam, what do you say? Yes,
they are not ordinary people either.
No, no, do not say that.
Enemy, but our nature
is slightly different.
Yes, I will explain, madam ..
- What is this?
- What a bad man
No, madam, you are telling
me, I will explain .. What is this?
Is this how to talk to a woman?
Brother, what is this insolence?
No, madam, you have to
say that this is part of the body.
Then I will
explain it correctly.
What do you explain?
No, no well, forget all of this.
These poor people won the
match just, and they are happy.
Where are they bothering?
- Without inconvenience?
My brother, they
spoiled the entire bus.
They came with drugs, and they
tried to give it to my son as well.
It is not a drug, but a powder.
- Powder.
- If it is powder, put it inside.
O man, the bus has
become a crazy clinic.
- Hey, uncle, come here.
- Yes, tell me.
Did your wife escape,
or is she about to escape?
If you are not crazy,
To slap you a slap that
leaves a trace on the road.
End, no problem.
Sir, the match ...the next when?
To hell in the match.
- What about the tournament?
- To hell in the championship.
Sir, what is this hell?
- Go ahead.
- I do not eat onions.
- Hey, Lotus.
- Welcome.
- Goodbye, sir ..
- Well, goodbye, who came to you?
- The girl, goodbye, sir.
- Farewell.
- Go ahead.
- I do not eat hot peppers either.
This is not a hot
pepper, it is a pepper.
Galaxy is also a
kind of pepper, right?
I do not eat it.
Sunil, do we go?
Sir, my uncle
came .. I am going.
- Well, okay go.
- I will go.
- Sunil Wait for a minute.
- Yes.
Your shoes are a solution,
hold this for a minute.
I am waiting.
Thank you, sir, for the Lord to bless you .. I am going.
- Good.
What do you eat, madam?
- I do not eat pepper.
Do not eat pepper,
do not eat onions.
- Anything else?
- No.
- All.
- Thanks..
Punto?
Does Judo eat?
- Please, sir.
- No no.
Please, sir, it's completely empty.
- You go.
Sonita ..
Wait a minute, only four weeks
have passed in my own room.
Not on my song, son.
Sonita ..
Golshan.
- What do you
do? Sorry... sorry.
- What happened to your nose?
- You just hit him.
No, no, what did you do before?
He was injured.
Have you shocked again?
No, my dear.
Kindly extinguish this music.
How does the team play?
- Win two games.
When is the next match?
I came to talk about that ..
Please remove this .. I
cannot take care of this team.
I cannot take care of
these 30 -year -old children.
You cannot even take
care of a sixth child.
Who, your cousin's children?
Please, these are not
children, but young demons.
Is this reason you imprisoned
the little in the bathroom?
My God, he was spending his need
and the door is open, what should I do?
Three years have passed, and even today,
the sister Benke did not even talk to me.
You should thank me.
As you were a good intimate friend,
you are now a strange husband.
All intimate friends
are good, of course.
Why? Because they do
not bear any responsibility.
Responsible?
You did not carry a
gas cylinder in your life.
And you talk about
assuming responsibilities.
O Golshan, one day everyone
should assume responsibilities.
This team gives you an
opportunity to be responsible, man.
But I train them, my dear ..
I am their coach and not their
father, to run behind them everywhere.
You are not the
father of anyone.
Your father left you and left.
So you think that all
parents will do that.
You make fun of your mother
because she is afraid of darkness.
Mocked me because I
am afraid of the lizards.
But the most cowardly
is you Golshan.
You are afraid to
become a father.
My coming here was wrong.
I am going.
Why did you come?
To ask for help.
So request it.
I don't want to order anything.
I made a very big
mistake to come here.
Forgive me, that is enough.
Once again, you run
away from the conversation.
Running responsibilities.
That team is your
responsibility, that's all.
So, do you say that it became like Sharman Kumar
and carried them on my shoulder here and there?
The matches are in different places,
sometimes here and sometimes there.
I will not sit with this team
on a public bus or train.
Good.
- So he rented a small bus.
- There is no budget.
I will find a small
bus for you, let's go.
Really, then who will lead
it? My license has gone.
My team does not have licenses.
Do something, since you
feel all this love towards them ..
Bring you the bus,
and protect it yourself.
Truly?
Why did you come here?
Do you think I am your driver?
Am I so foolish,
to leave my work ..
To drive your bus
here and there?
- No, I mean, let's discuss.
- No no.
Please, is it big?
- No.
Thanks.
Have you heard the sound?
It seems as if a love
bird screams on the bus.
Isn't it?
Madam, deal with the transmission
with caution please, it's very sensitive.
Madam, do not manage the
steering wheel strongly, sorry .. but ..
Madam, something else,
do not give her to the master.
Otherwise, he will do my
car as he does in his car.
Do we go, brother, what
happens .. Come on.
I said that as a matter of humor,
I wish you a happy journey.
Yes, a happy trip
.. Come, comrades.
Lotus, Lotus ..
Pay attention, focus.
Our opponent team seems a group
of scum, to strip them of their clothes.
- No..
- Why?
We came to win, not to end them.
One, two, three ..
Cetari ..
Come on, guys.
However, the Cetary team
qualified for the semi -finals.
Wonderful, isn't it, sir, coach?
Today in the semi -finals, the Cetary
team will face its opponent Basket Guru.
Go ahead Golo, run ..
Go, Golo, pass it to Sonile.
The basket, oh Sunil basket.
Amazing.
Wonderful guys .. Go
back again, return again.
Oh Golo, wonderful Golo Go.
Lotus .. Lotus.
Amazing..
I really did
something wonderful.
No, my coach's lady is the
one who did something great.
Welcome?
Come on, guys
...retreat... retreat.
Oh, Panto.
Why clean your ear, go there.
Wonderful Panto, do
whatever you want, well?
All you have to
do is enjoy playing.
Hey Panto, clean your
ear, well, wonderful Panto.
My God, my lady, you are here ..
I didn't even see you.
Wonderful, sir, coach.
Thank you, madam ..
Madam, please sit, let's go.
Hey Panto, move away.
Take it, oh Sunil .. basket ..
- Register..
- Wonderful Sonel.
In the last stage of the match, the
Cetary team advances 12 points.
Hargovind.
Good morning, sir.
I haven't seen you long ago.
This team and this tournament are
gaining wide popularity on social media.
As well as this coach.
This coach is good.
- I like it.
- One .. two .. three .. Cetary.
The dreaded is a good
coach, but he is as a man ..
He will learn.
We train it.
He has a shortage here.
This is not true.
But he will learn to live
with this deficiency as well.
Well, I will go now
.. I see you later.
Yes, Golo .. Go Golo ..
With this victory, the Cetary
team qualifies for the final match.
A minute, minute ..
Hargovind.
The team plays well, it
has reached the finals.
You are part of the team too ..
You will play in
the finals, right?
You want this team to win
at any cost, right, sir, coach?
Yes.
You are short.
But you are a great man.
Thanks.
But will you play or not?
Hey Hargovind.
There is nothing wrong,
sir, coach, continue to try.
You know anger from a young age.
If you try to try, also
learn how to convince.
I am trying.
Please stop him.
I am talking about you.
Why can we not
be together again?
The past few days and me ..
I was thinking
about talking to you.
I am thinking of
trying to convince you.
So convinced me.
Who stops you?
Vanity.
He is a friend since childhood.
He became part of me
and will never leave me.
Oh Sonita, whatever the
length of a man or husband ..
His arrogance rises
100 feet in the air.
And I know ..
I have a lot of wrong
things that you don't like.
Every time I go out, I
ask for ready -to -eat food.
I wear athletic shoes with pants,
I have no sense of elegance.
I do not recognize any
singer except Kumar Sano.
If anyone is a little
different from me, mock him.
Now, what do I do?
This is what I saw and learned from a
young age, and I do the same thing ..
But now I am trying to change.
At least I understood ..
That not all you learned
in childhood was true.
So I try to give
up wrong things.
And the right things ..
Hold it 💞
Hey Sonita, I know we
have become a problem.
Can we not return
a couple again?
Please?
Yes, oh Golshan.
But I want to be more
than just a couple.
I want a third person
to come to our lives.
Do I take an intimate friend?
- Golshan stop, I am
talking seriously. Sorry, sorry.
I want to become a
mother, I can't wait more.
I understand that, but ..
Golshan.
How long will you
continue to make excuses?
It is not that easy,
right Sonita?
At this age we want
to become fathers.
You also know...
At this age...
...There is a very
high possibility to be ..
What .. what?
For children to have
Down syndrome, or autism.
Our children may
be like them, my dear.
What?
I am talking
realistically, my dear.
Hi, sir.
I also do not want
my child to be ..
Gay.
Sorry Sonel, I
did not mean that ..
I really said that ..
I .. I said ..
I am not so fool.
I know that no one wants
to have a child like me.
They want a healthy child.
But they want a father like you.
Sir, the coach, all
you have done so far,
You want it with
all your heart ..
On that, I want to tell you
thank you and I am very grateful.
Please, forgive me Sonita
I was the national
gold medal champion.
Patriotism?
Those with special needs.
I was the captain
of the Delhi team.
But my medal was robbed of me.
Why?
Our coach committed injustice.
There were two in the team ..
They had no Down
syndrome and no united.
They had nothing ..
They played forged certificates.
The coach wanted
to win at any cost.
He did not trust us.
Since that day, I no
longer trust any coach.
When I was eight ..
My father left us and left.
Since that day, I could
not trust anyone either.
I always felt that everyone
would abandon me.
Before someone abandoned me ..
Do any play ..
And move away from them.
I completely tired.
I was only eight.
But as on that day, today ..
After that, I never cried.
Sir, I saw my mother
crying only once in my life.
When my medal was
taken away from me.
Ma ..
My mother .. I know
that you were very sad.
When the gold medal
was robbed of Hargovind.
- But sir, coach .. No
Hargovind, let me speak.
Because one coach was wrong, it does not
mean that all the coaches will be wrong.
Trust me.
- Oh my God, but my son I ..
- This stubbornness.
I see this stubbornness
in my eyes Hargovind.
Your son is completely
similar to you.
Give him your approval, mom ..
We will definitely
return the gold medal.
I will accept your feet ..
- My mom..
- Sir, the coach, it is not my mother.
It is the aunt mangit
from the adjacent house.
This is my mother.
Welcome.
My mother, sorry, my aunt ..
All you said now,
say it here too.
Hargovind.
The coach who cried my mother ..
He left.
But the coach who laughed her ..
Trust it, my dear,
say to him, mom ..
I tell him to play
a long time ago.
He does not listen.
Play again, son, play.
- I will play, sir.
- Oh my God, this is wonderful.
Mom, bring some shirt.
- Good. Now the
gold medal for us.
Come embrace me, my lord.
Oh Fahdi.
Hargovind, thank you.
To trust you.
Thanks.
What do you say Carter Baji?
Our team qualifies for the finals,
yet we will not go to the match?
The finals in
Mumbai, sir, coach.
Yes, and what about that?
This is good, children
will also see the sea.
The trip by train is very long,
they may not be able to go.
We do not have a budget for
flying, hotels and such things.
I did not expect
to reach the final.
So we spent all the money
that we had on previous matches.
This is not fair.
Children's hearts will crash.
Sir, the coach, to this day.
What they got
according to their desire?
Nevertheless, they smile.
They know how to be happy.
We are crying ..
Wonderful, look
very happy today.
No, mom, I am sad.
But you are smiling.
Sad from the inside.
Why, what happened?
No, no, nothing.
Tell me.
Forget it, nothing.
Raju.
- Everything will be fine, well?
- What happened?
Everything will be fine ..
I will go outside
for a few days.
Do not follow the house
or anything in my absence ..
Where are you going?
To the Temple of Teachers ..
- The taxi arrived.
When will you return?
When one goes to do good,
he does not ask such questions.
When I will return .. I will
return after a few days.
My mom...
What Golshan?
- The taxi arrived.
- Tell me.
The taxi arrived.
Just go out, go now.
The taxi has arrived.
The taxi has arrived...
Good.
- Let's go...
- Come on, let us.
Sir, a sound was issued from the piston
today .. Did any accident occur, sir?
Where Sonita?
- I saw signs of scratches, sir.
- Sonita.
- Here I am.
What do you want now?
I want an actress.
Will I find one?
- Sonita, forgive me on that day...
- I don't care about your apology.
I just come for the
team, not for you.
No .. I understand that.
Let's focus on the work
we came to accomplish.
It is as follows, sir, we
follow all the laws here.
We play gambling
at the time of Diwali.
As far as we win, the
money also goes to the police.
Nothing happens
illegal here, madam.
We renewed the license
the day before yesterday.
Likewise, the food inspector prepared
a great report on us, Madam, listen.
Let me tell you an
order, in all Delhi...
Nobody attends
the signifier of me.
Now that you come,
let me go and then go.
Do you know what this is?
Memory memory.
It is not a portable
memory, my uncle G.
- If?
- Guide.
Evidence of employees.
You are employing a young
man here Karim Quraishi.
You hire him with half a salary.
You make him 12 hours
and you say it's 8 hours.
Pover, and talk to
him in a bad way.
This means that a person faces intellectual challenges
that are exposed daily to psychological and physical abuse.
You will face at
least eight charges.
At least...
You will have to meditate for
three years in Tihar prison.
Also, the signifier of
Makhani, who promises it...
Nobody promises it like you.
So, can you bring
two layers here?
Oh this, what is your name?
Brother?
Can we not settle this
matter between us?
- Do you offer a bribe to the lady?
- No no.
Not bribery.
Kahwi for children.
Madam for your children...
Hey, not children.
- Children... no...
Well, no children...
Yes.
Now listen to what
you should do...
A plane... a plane...
Where are you going?
- His boss seized tickets and hotel.
- Yes... wonderful.
I got fifteen days...
- vacation. Really,
this is very cool.
Whoever says there are
no good people in the world.
I will definitely invite you
as well as for your boss.
Thanks.
I wish you success
My sister, can you not
stop this plane on the left?
Why?
No, the journey to
Colkata at eight o'clock.
It can go and collide
with a plane Mumbai.
- Good... Congratulations.
Welcome.
How are you?
Hargovind.
It is good that you are
coming to the finals.
Thanks.
Frankly, sir, since the
day your wife came...
I feel the desire
to join the team.
We got the rooms, comrades.
Listen, to share the rooms.
Two people in one room, well?
- Godo and Satbir.
- Two present.
So, Lotus and Sonile?
Hargovind Stay
with Carters Baji.
Well, sir.
Sonita, you are staying...
Sonita while I am in
one room... that's all.
Please explain.
Sharma G says you
will stay in his room.
Sharma J?
Did you start understanding
what Sharma G says?
Sharma J.
Sorry, Sharma G, I
will stay with Gulo.
I have a lover,
do not try to spin.
Sharma G, keep you with Karim.
Raju, Panto...
This is my room...
Come, to go up to the top.
Sonita, ascend
them in the elevator.
I will go up on the
stairs a little... well?
Sir, sir, pardon, seventh floor.
Sir, go in the elevator.
Otherwise, you will hurt you.
No, no, I will get
some exercises.
Because Golshan
is afraid of elevators.
He was stuck once
when he was young.
Since that day, he does
not use the elevator.
Look, take them in the elevator.
I will come from the
stairs, well... goodbye.
Goodbye, sir... Goodbye, sir...
- Go, go. Sir, sir.
There is a snake...
snake?
Where?
Oh my God, Golshan,
are you okay?
Golshan, are you okay?
Nothing will happen,
it's just an elevator.
Close your mouths
...the elevator will fall.
Do not be afraid.
- Let's go down.
- My God, it is an elevator that can accommodate six people.
Look, he will not be able
to bear all this weight.
Sir, it is not good to
describe anyone as the body.
I did not describe
anyone with the body.
I said, your saying
'weight' means a debt.
- My mother... Calm down.
Click on the alarm bell.
No, no, close your mouths.
Click on the emergency bell.
Sorry, madam.
I think the elevator is
stuck, madam, a moment...
There are players inside.
- Related?
We are about to die.
Before we die, I will
bid farewell to my love.
I have an idea... when the
scooter kicks it, it begins to work.
Yes, and the
elevator will also work.
So, let us all cry
together, soldiers.
Let's go...
No, no, no...
Oh my God, are you okay?
Water, water...
Sir, we are alive here,
nothing happened to you, sir.
No one dies from
riding the elevator, sir.
Sir, where were you?
I was in the elevator.
You did not die.
You did not die,
you did not die, sir.
You have been overwhelmed
by your fear, just like me.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I overcame fear.
I did not come.
I am alive.
The elevator was
great. Thank you, mom.
I already installed
the elevator twice.
My lion cub is my own...
So, how are you in the retired?
Wonderful, wonderful.
Well, my mother, I will
ride the elevator again.
This time I will shoot
and send it to you, well?
Allo my mom?
I don't hear you, Alo?
- My mother... Alo...
- Alo...
Here, my son has returned.
Yes, yes, this is not,
what is your hotel name?
My mom, are you
not in the retirement?
Here you have
started shouting again.
If I am not in the
retired, where will I be?
Oh my life...
Alo Golo.
My mom?
The bathroom...
- water...
brown...
Hey, did you eat the
signifier here, it's great.
Mom, is this time to
talk about the signifier?
How long has this happen?
How long did this
start Dalaat G?
Debavali?
When did you send me a "I
wish you a speedy recovery" card?
Your leg was injured
during Choti Holly, right?
Isn't it Golo, am I right?
Do not talk to me, please.
My mother, I will never
accept this, I told you.
Golshan, if your mother
has a lover, in that...
Do not use this word.
- Please...
- So what do you call it?
My daughter, he is right...
I also don't like this word.
Say it is a good
friend, a close friend...
Am I right, Golshan?
- Don't talk to me, please.
I am waiting.
- What?
- I must open the panto clouds.
Does he want to urinate?
- If?
- What if I need it at night?
Mom, this...
- What is there?
- Who is this?
This is my mother.
Hello son.
Coach, your father looks great.
Thank you, son.
- Hey, this is not my father, Alo...
- Yes, children.
- Alo.
- Hello son.
Mom, this is a mistake.
This is a mistake, I tell
you, this is very wrong.
I knew you would say this...
For this reason
I did not tell you.
You never support your mother...
And why should I support you?
Because I always support you.
I changed the house
for your training.
I took you to the
competitions on the scooter.
Have you seen a short
basketball player in your life?
No, no, I have never
seen it, it's the first.
His coach was not
even ready to test him.
I slapped him strongly on
his face, just kissing his test.
Also, on Tuesday.
He was not allowed to eat
meat until Tuesday, ask him.
- Sir, did you do that?
- Yes, and what is that?
Whether you are right or
wrong, I support you in everything.
- Why?
Because it is my team.
Never give up your team.
Yes, sir, you never
give up your team.
Golshan, never
My mom.
Why are you crying?
Enough, do not cry... please.
Never give up your team...
- Oh, move away.
What?
Is Panto clouds open?
- Yes.
- This is the coach's father.
Hey, not my father, Alo?
- Alo...
- What happens here?
- You are very handsome.
Thank you, son...
Look, why did you
all come to my room?
- Godo, this is not my father.
- Yes, it's your father.
Godo, he is not my father.
- It is not my father.
- Decent.
Children are very honest.
They say they are
a picture of the Lord.
Children said you are handsome.
- Yes, the children admired the new father.
Goodbye, my son, goodbye.
Goodbye, my daughter...
Goodbye... Goodbye Golo.
- Good night, states J.
- Good night and happy dreams, son...
Enter, enter?
They return to the room itself.
What is your problem?
Your mother's life or her lover?
Both of them.
Golshan.
Can't the mother enjoy
her own life as well?
Oh my God, mothers have no life.
What did you just say?
Did you say that you
support your mother or not?
Yes, I said that, but...
I cannot change overnight.
It is enough for me to be proud
that I did not suffocate Galaat G.
Time passes.
Then tomorrow our final match.
And above all
this, this problem.
Just try.
- Does it succeed, right? Never.
Come to go on a tour.
Let's go.
Let's go up in the elevator,
and let us film a video.
Good.
I don't feel the desire to
send him to my mother now.
Cetary .. Cetary ..
Sir, their name is
the young players.
But they don't
seem like that, right?
Don't worry, they
are all average.
Oh my God, what is the
problem in length .. We must fight.
Sir, this battle does
not seem friendly.
Come, let's go home.
O Sonel, these are
the national chain finals.
We will win, because we are...
Cetary .. Cetary ..
But hear, wear the
helmet tightly today.
Good.
Amazing.
Go and defend.
Hargovind, wonderful.
Amazing.
Stop it, raise your hands.
Sunil, stop it.
Sonil, you couldn't stop him.
Sir, my finger
has been twisting.
Sunil, this is not the time
of exaggeration in everything.
Look at this.
Sunil, you should
go to a doctor.
- Go out now.
- No, sir.
The team needs me, sir.
I am going, I have to go.
Look at this.
But after the match ended,
he took him to a doctor.
So as not to spread infection.
Otherwise, you will have
to amputate the entire arm.
Go, Hargovind.
Wonderful Lotus,
pass it to Golo.
O group, the time is over.
Team, come here, comrades.
O comrades, you understood
what the problem is.
Nani Khailadi team has
players throughout the stature.
Our team has short players.
Now I will show you how
to defeat the long short.
Make your weakness
your strength.
It is difficult for young
players like us to jump high.
But it is difficult for the
long players to bend.
So from now on,
all high passes...
Aerobic passes, the
balls sent from the top...
All are canceled.
We will pass
everything from below.
Passes, pass from the bottom.
Pass the ball with a
bounce, did you understand?
Yes, sir.
Well, these long
tall exhausted us.
Now it's the role
of the little finger.
Come on, comrades,
one, two, three .. Steari.
Amazing.
Lotus, pass the ball.
Wonderful, wonderful.
Amazing.
We just tried for two minutes.
- Two minutes only.
- Yes, coach.
- I want to give it to everyone.
- One, two, three ..
- Cetari.
Come on, guys,
there is nothing wrong.
Come on, guys... retreat.
Stop it, raise your hands.
Go, Hargovind, there
are still 20 seconds.
We can still win, go.
Hargovind, pass the ball.
Cream, to the basket.
Go Karim .. Go.
Oh my God, what do
you do Karim .. there.
Cetary .. Cetary ..
Golo, we lost.
We won, sir.
We lost.
No, sir, we won second place.
This is what I mean by loss.
Sir, my mother says that
two are better than one.
Two .. two.
Sir, we enjoyed
...very wonderful.
We love you, Mr. Golshan.
Hug me.
Sonita.
I am not their coach Sonita.
They are my coach.
I always underestimate them.
But today I realized that
the shortage was really in me.
They understand the
happiness and sorrows of others.
While I couldn't even
understand what others say.
My thinking is only...
Inspection of anyone else.
This may be the biggest
defect in the world.
I underestimated them.
The heart of one
is very large...
How can this be
a defect in them?
I love you Golshan.
Lotus.
Six.
- Welcome.
- Mr. Araora.
Good morning.
Yes, Baswan.
I have seen what extent
did you reach your team.
I will retire next month.
You nominated your
name to replace my local.
The administration agreed.
As of next month, you are the
coach of the Delhi basketball team.
Did you nominate my name?
Golshan Aroura.
As a man, you are a pig.
But you are a great coach.
It seems that the man
has improved a little now.
Congratulations, coach.
Thank you, sir.
Who was this?
Nothing, go back to sleep.
What happened?
Everyone should
go at the end, coach.
What really matters is...
How do we face challenges
when it comes at the time.
I did a great job.
In fact, your three
months ended.
However, we kept you
for an additional month.
Until the championship ends.
Thank you, coach.
Children would be very happy if you
met them before you go, do I call them?
No, no, I .. no need.
In fact, I'm late, I have to go.
As you like.
Tell them goodbye on my behalf.
Keep the keys to
this cabinet with you.
The new coach who will replace your
shop has arrived, waiting at the bottom.
Give it to him.
Good.
I will go.
Good luck.
These keys...
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I have not met anyone yet.
How is the team?
Amazing.
Initially, it will take
some time to adapt.
You will not understand
what Mr. Sharma says.
The cream method in intermittent
conversation will make you mad.
You will feel that
everyone is strange.
You will feel like
stuck somewhere.
But little by little...
You will start feeling
that everything is fine.
The actions Godo and Sonil...
You will start
understanding it in the end.
Lotus, you will get used to
seeing a new hair color every week.
Golo...
Gossip Satber...
You will start feeling great.
Just do not make a mistake
that you are smarter than them.
They are smarter
than me and you.
When you teach them,
You will learn much more.
Also, do not reprimand them.
They are very sensitive.
Do not get angry
with anything they do.
Their hearts are very pure.
And also...
When it is time to leave...
Do not leave without
bid them farewell.
Hi, sir.
Hello sir.
I will leave you all and leave.
And then...
We have been together only.
Sir, are you about to die?
What?
Sir, will you die?
- No.
- So why do you speak like this...
- Why?
- No no.
It is about to die.
It hides the matter.
The master is about to die.
Oh my God, shut up.
Shut up.
Oh my God, do
not bark like dogs.